Milch Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Miscellaneous, 1916-1970, undated, Series 6:
  - Shipping receipts (bound), prepaid, cont., 1955-1965 (Reel 4465)
Dec. 18-Jan. 16, 1920 Annual Holiday Exhibition of Selected Paintings of Limited Size by American Artists
Dec. 29-Jan. 15, 1920* Portraits and Other Paintings by Royston Nave
Feb. 2-14, 1920 George Biddle
Feb. 2-14, 1920* Oil Paintings, Water Colors, Pastels, Monotypes, Silver-Points and Etchings by George Biddle
Feb. 16-28, 1920* Paintings by Ossip L. Linde
March 1-12, 1920 Bruce Crane
March 1-13, 1920 Bruce Crane, A.N.A.
March 15-April 3, 1920 Willard L. Metcalf
April 5-20, 1920 Paintings
April 8-30 [1920] Exhibition of Paintings by Leading American Artists
April 15-May 1, 1920 Valentino Molina
Oct. 18-30 [1920?]* Paintings of New England and Drawings of the Devastated Towns of Flanders by George Wharton Edwards
Nov. 1-13, 1920 Six American Painters [Clark, Potthast, Snell, Nichols, Olinsky, and Volkert
Nov. 1-15, 1920 Paintings by Theresa F. Bernstein
Nov. 15-27, 1920 Childe Hassam
Nov. 21-Dec. 3, 1920* Sculpture by Gleb Derujinsky
Dec., 1920* Exhibition by George Biddle
Dec. 1-21, 1920 Etchings and Color Etchings by William Meyerowitz
Dec. 27-Jan. 28, 1921 Albert Delbert Smith
circa 1920 Ossip L. Linde
circa 1920 William Meyrowitz
circa 1920 Exhibition
Jan. 10-29, 1921 Exhibition of Paintings by Brush, Crane, Dewing, Metcalf, Hassam, and Murphy
Jan. 31-Feb. 12, 1921 American Art
Feb. 14-26, 1921 Guy Wiggins
Feb. 14-26, 1921 Arthur G. Goodwin
Feb. 28-March 12, 1921 Paintings by Robert Henri
March 14-April 9, 1921 Paintings by Gari Melchers
March 28-April 9, 1921 Peter Marcus
April 11-23, 1921* Portraits and Figure Paintings by Edith Catlin Phelps
April 11-30, 1921 Paintings by Willard Metcalf
May 2-30, 1921 American Sculpture for the Town and Country House, the Garden, and the Grounds
Oct. 18-30 [1921?]* Paintings and Drawings by George Wharton Edwards
Oct. 24-Nov. 5, 1921 Portraits and Paintings of Old New Orleans by Wayman Adams
Nov. 7-19, 1921 Flower Paintings and Sculpture by Mathilde Browne
Nov. 7-19, 1921 Paintings in Oil and Water Color by George H. Clements
Nov. 19-Dec. 3, 1921 Sculpture-Gleb Derujinsky
Dec. 5-31, 1921 Works by Abbott H. Thayer, Including Important Paintings, Water Colors, and Drawings
circa 1921 Exhibition
Jan. 9-21, 1922 Paintings by Katherine Langhorne Adams
Jan. 9-21, 1922 Paintings of California by Douglass Ewell Parshall
Feb. 13-March 4, 1922 Paintings of Cape Ann by Harry A. Vincent, A.N.A.
March 6-25, 1922* Pastels of the Cascapedia River, Canada, by Arthur C. Goodwin
March 6-25, 1922 Connecticut Landscape Paintings by Wilson Irvine
March 27-April 15, 1922* Moonlight Motifs: Garden of the Gods, Colorado and Other Paintings by Robert Reid, N.A.
Dec. 26-Jan. 13, 1923 Paintings and Pastels by Henry C. White
Jan. 15-27, 1923* Paintings of Spain by William J. Potter
Jan. 29-Feb. 10, 1923 Water Colors of the South Sea Islands by William Ritschel, N.A.
Feb. 12-March 3, 1923 Paintings by Willard L. Metcalf
March 5-31, 1923 Paintings of the Far East by Leon Gaspard
March 19-31, 1923* Landscape Paintings by Guy Wiggins, A.N.A.
April 2-21, 1923* Portrait Drawings by Ercole Cartotto
April 19-May 6, 1923 Paintings by Leading American Artists
Oct. 1-20, 1923 Paintings by Sidney E. Dickinson, A.N.A.
Oct. 22- Nov. 3, 1923 Paintings and Sculpture by Mathilda Brown (Mrs. Frederick Van Wyck)
Nov. 5-17, 1923 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings by William Gedney Bunce
Dec. 11-23, 1923* Water Colors by James Montgomery Flagg
Jan. 14-26, 1924 Exhibition of Nudes, Portraits, Landscapes and Genre by Eugene Paul Ullman
Feb. 18-March 8, 1924 Paintings by Willard L. Metcalf
March 27-April 5, 1924 Connecticut Landscapes by Guy Wiggins, A.N.A.
Dec. 1-27, 1924 Maurice Fromkes
Jan. 5-17, 1925 Paintings of the Pacific Coast by Armin Hansen
Jan. 19-31, 1925 Martha Walter
Feb. 16-March 7, 1925 Willard L. Metcalf
March 9-21, 1925 John Noble
March 23-April 11, 1925 Bruce Crane
May 4-16, 1925 Brynjulf Strandenaes Exhibition of Portraits
May 18-30, 1925 Paintings by Robert Brackman
Dec. 7-31, 1925 Paintings by the Late Willard Metcalf
Dec. 7-21, 1925 Sketches by Dorothea A. Dreier,
Jan. 11-23, 1926 Recent Landscape Paintings by Frank V. Du Mond
Jan. 25-Feb. 13, 1926 Smaller Paintings by Max Bohm
Feb. 15-March 6, 1926 Paintings of the Sea by William Ritschel
April 13-May 2, 1926 Jonas Lie
April 26-May 15, 1926 Landscapes and Street Scenes by William Jean Beauley
Nov. 15-27, 1926 California Marine Paintings and Water Colors by Armin Hansen
Nov. 29-Dec. 18, 1926 Water Colors by Frank W. Benson
Nov. 29-Dec. 18, 1926 Silver-Point Drawings by Ercole Cartotto
Jan. 10-22, 1927 Portraits by Millie Bruhl Frederick (Mrs. Leopold Fredrick)
Jan. 24-Feb. 12, 1927 Paintings of Cornwall and Devonshire by W. Elmer Schofield
Jan. 24-Feb. 12, 1927 Etchings by Teresa Cerutti Simmons, Watercolors by Will Simmons
Feb. 14-March 5, 1927 Sculpture by Heinz Warneke
March 28-April 16, 1927 Paintings by Henry Golden Dearth
April 18-30, 1927 Decorative Flower Paintings by Olin Howland
April 18-30, 1927 Recent Water Colors by John Whorf of Boston
Oct. 10-28, 1927 Decorative Embroideries by Georgiana Brown Harbeson
Nov. 14-26, 1927 Pastels and Etchings of Cambodia and China by Lucille Douglass
Nov. 28-Dec. 24, 1927 Works by Gari Melchers
Nov. 28-Dec. 24, 1927 Sculpture by Max Kalish
Dec. 26-Jan. 14, 1928 Water Color Exhibition of West African Native Types by Erick Berry; Also a Group of West African Pottery and Brass Figures Made by the Natives of Nigeria
Dec. 29-Jan. 14, 1928 Paintings by Joacb Dooyewaard
Jan. 14-26, 1928 Decorative Paintings by Jane Peterson
Feb. 7-April 29, 1928 Alfred Hutty
Feb. 13-25, 1928 Water Colors by Alice Judson
March 12-24, 1928 Etchings of Ancient Dances by Teresa Cerutti-Simmons and Wild Life by Will Simmons
March 12-24, 1928 An Important Exhibition of Paintings and Pastels by John H. Twachtman
March 12-24, 1928 Sculpture by Heinz Warnecke
March 26-April 14, 1928 Water Colors by John Whorf
April, 1928 Water Colors by William Ritschel, N.A.
April 15-May 5, 1928 Portrait Drawings in Pastel by Jessie Voss Lewis
Oct. 22-Nov. 3, 1928 Water Colors of France and Italy, and Etchings by Louis Wolchonok
Oct. 22-Nov. 3, 1928 Poetic Landscapes with Figures by Henry M. Rosenberg of Nova Scotia
Nov. 19-Dec. 1, 1928 Water Colors by Frank W. Benson
Nov. 19-Dec. 1, 1928 Water Colors of Architectural Subjects in France, Also Landscape and Figures by William de Leftwick Dodge
Dec. 1-28, 1928 Alfred Hutty
Dec. 3-24, 1928 Important Exhibition of Early and Recent Works by Childe Hassam of the American Academy of Arts and Letters
Dec. 3-24, 1928 Still Life Paintings by Ruth Payne Burgess
Dec. 20-Jan. 8, 1929 Drawings by Frank di Gioia
Dec. 20-Jan. 8, 1929 Memorial Exhibition, Water Color Sketches by Thomas Moran, N.A.
Dec. 27-Jan. 14, 1929 Erick Berry
Dec. 27-Jan. 14, 1929 Helen K. McCarthy Memorial Exhibition
Dec. 29-Jan. 14, 1929 Paintings by Jacob Dooyewaard
circa 1928 Indian and Animal Pictures and Bronzes by Edwin Willard Deming
Jan. 28-Feb. 9, 1929 Painitings of Western Life by F. Tenney Johnson
Jan. 28-Feb. 9, 1929 Paintings and Water Colors by Alice Judson
Feb. 11-23, 1929 Paintings and Drawings by Max Bohm
Feb. 11-23, 1929 Landscapes and Marines by Jay Connaway
Feb. 25-March 9, 1929 Water-Colors by Harold Putnam Browne
Feb. 25-March 9, 1929 Paintings by Truman Fassett
March 11-23, 1929 Recent Water Colors by C.E. Polowetski
March 11-23, 1929 Louis Ritman
March 25-April 6, 1929 Landscapes by Frank Vincent Du Mond
March 25-April 6, 1929 Water Colors by Armin Hansen of California
March 25-April 6, 1929 Sculptures by Roy Sheldon
April 8-20, 1929 Water Colors by John Whorf, Distinguished Young Boston Artist
Oct. 21-Nov. 2, 1929 Corners in Spain, An Exhibition of Paintings by Wells M. Sawyer
Nov. 4-17, 1929 Recent Sculpture by Heinz Warnecke
Nov. 4-16, 1929 Paintings of Ireland and Other Scenes by Power O'Malley
Nov. 18-30, 1929 Group of Recent Paintings by Hayley Lever
Nov. 18-30, 1929 Recent Water Colors and Etchings by Louis Wolchonok
Dec. 2-21, 1929 Paintings by Maurice Fromkes
Jan. 30-Feb. 11 [192?] Water Colors of Greek Temples in Sicily by Wm. De Leftwich Dodge
Feb. 2-15 [192?] Figure Paintings by Murray Bewley
March 15-April 3 [192?] Paintings by Willard L. Metcalf
March 28-April 16 [192?] Paintings by Henry Golden Dearth
April 2-21 [192?] Landscape Paintings by Bruce Crane, N.A
Oct. 17-29 [192?] Water Colors of the Rivera by Ferris Connah
Oct. 18-30 Paintings and Drawings by George Wharton Edwards
Oct. 25-Nov. 13 [192?] Recent Landscapes by John F. Carlson, N.A.
Oct. 25-Nov. 13 [192?] John F. Carlson
Nov. 19-Dec. 1 [192?] Water Colors of Architectural Subjects in France, also Landscape and Figures by William De Leftwich Dodge
[192?] Indian and Animal Pictures and Bronzes by Edwin Willard Deming
Jan. 20-Feb 1, 1930 West African Water Colors by Erick Berry
Jan. 20-Feb. 1, 1930 Paintings by Nelson C. White
Feb., 1930 Thelma Wood
Feb. 3-15, 1930 Paintings by Horace Brown
Feb. 17-March 1, 1930 Paintings by Francis Speight
Feb. 17-March 1, 1930 Paintings by Ruth Payne Burgess
March 3-15, 1930 Paintings by John Noble
March 17-29, 1930 Russian Paintings by Irwin D. Hoffman, Also a Group of Recent Watercolors
March 17-29, 1930 Alexander Warshawsky
March 31-April 12, 1930 Memorial Exhibition, Paintings and Watercolors of Sigurd Skou
March 31-April 12, 1930 Emmanuel Andrew Cavacos
April 14-26, 1930 Water Colors by John Whorf
Oct. 20-Nov. 1, 1930 Recent Paintings of Lake Como by Charles Warren Eaton
Nov. 3-15, 1930 Pastels and Etchings of Angkor and the Far East by Lucille Douglass
Nov. 17-29, 1930 Joseph Szekely
Nov. 17-29, 1930 Important Exhibiton of Paintings by a "Group of Americans"
Dec. 1-13, 1930 Diana Thorne and Canine Portraiture
Dec. 1-13, 1930 Recent Paintings of Ireland by Power O'Malley
Dec. 1-13, 1930 Paintings by Charles M. Cox of Boston
Jan. 19-31, 1931 Portraits by Jere R. Wickwire
Jan. 20-Feb. 1, 1931 Nelson C. White
Jan. 24-Feb. 7, 1931 Pastels and Etchings of Angkor and the Far East by Lucille Douglass
Feb. 2-24, 1931 Recent Paintings by Lillian Gentle
Feb. 2-24, 1931 Impressions of India and Palestine by Ruth Coleman
Feb. 16-28, 1931 Watercolors of Vermont Scenes and Other Views by Ruth Payne Burgess
Feb. 16-28, 1931 Martha Walter Recent Work in Oil and Watercolor
March 2-14, 1931 Recent Paintings by Alice Judson
March 2-28, 1931 Paintings & Drawings by Gari Melchers
March 16-28, 1931 Recent Watercolors by Harold Putnam Brown
March 30-April 11, 1931 Paintings by Louis Kronberg
March 30-April 11, 1931 Watercolors by John Whorf
April 13-25, 1931 Americans by American Artists, Exhibition of Portraits
April 13-25, 1931 Louis Kronberg
April 13-25, 1931 Portraits and Crayon Heads by Ferris Connah
April 13-May 2, 1931 Abbott H. Thayer
Sept. 22-Oct. 6, 1931 Water Colors by Gladys Brannigan, Alice Judson, Margery Ryerson
Oct. 19-30, 1931 Portraits by William Steene
Nov. 2-7, 1931 Portraits and Sketches by Maria Kammerer under the Patronage of Countess Laszlo Szechenyi
Nov. 9-21, 1931 Paintings by Bessie Lasky
Nov. 23-Dec. 5, 1931 Recent Oils, Water Colors and Etchings by Joseph Margulies
Dec. 7-21, 1931 Recent Paintings by George Wharton Edwards
Dec. 7-19, 1931 Paintings and Etchings of African and American Big Game by Major A. Radclyffe Dugmore
Dec. 7-19, 1931 Watercolors of Yucatan, "Land of the Mayas" by William de Leftwich Dodge
Dec. 20-Jan. 8, 1932 Water Colors of the Yellowstone and Mexican Series by Thomas Moran, N.A.
Jan. 11-23, 1932 Paintings, Watercolors and Etchings of Animals by Sybilla Mittell Weber
Jan. 25-Feb. 6, 1932 Paintings by George Oberteuffer, Member of the Salon d'Automne, Paris
Feb. 8-March 5, 1932 Important 19th and 20th Century American Painters
March 7-19, 1932 Paintings by Mrs. B. King Couper
March 7-19, 1932 Drawings by Maurice Sterne, Ernest Fiene, Alexander Brook, yasuo Kuniyoski, Bernard Karfiol, Peggy Bacon, and Leon Kroll
March 28-April 9, 1932 Watercolors by John Whorf
April 11-30, 1932 Forty Years of American Art
Oct. 3-15, 1932 New Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 19-Nov. 5, 1932 Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Nov. 7-30, 1932 Paintings by Edward Bruce
circa 1932 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Jan.30-Feb. 25, 1933 Important Exhibition of Paintings by Thomas Eakins
March 6-25, 1933 19th and 20th Century Watercolors
March 27-April 14, 1933 Paintings by Francis Speight
April 17-May 6, 1933 Water Colors by John Whorf
May 15-31, 1933 19th Century American Landscape Artists
Nov. 27-Dec., 1933 Water Colors by Emil Holzhaur
Feb. 26-March 17, 1934 Paintings by Stephen Etnier
March 19-April 7, 1934 Water Colors by John Whorf
April 16-May 5, 1934 Bali Studies by Maurice Sterne
June-Aug., 1934 Paintings by American Artists
Sept., 1934 Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 15-Nov. 3, 1934 New and Recent Paintings by American Artists
Nov. 5-21, 1934 Paintings by Sidney Laufman
Nov. 26-Dec., 1934 Recent Vermont Landscapes by Edward Bruce
circa 1934 American Figure Paintings of the 19th and 20th Century
Jan. 7-26, 1935 Paintings and Watercolors from the Samuel Halpert Estate
Feb. 4-28, 1935 Small Paintings by 19th and 20th Century American Artists
March 4-22, 1935 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etneir
March 25-April 13, 1935 Water Colors by John Whorf
April 22-May 11, 1935 Figure and Landscape Studies by Leon Kroll
May 20-June, 1935 Group Exibhition of Paintings
Summer, 1935 Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 1-26, 1935 Paintings by Childe Hassam
Oct. 28-Nov. 16, 1935 Watercolors by Millard Sheets
through Dec., 1935 Paintings by Americans
Jan. 1936 Paintings by Americans
Feb. 3-29, 1936 Important Exhibition of 19th and 20th Century American Painters
March 2-21, 1936 Stephen Etnier
March 30-April 19, 1936 Watercolors by John Whorf
May 18-June, 1936 Paintings by American Artists
Summer, 1936 Paintings by American Artists
September, 1936 Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 12-31, 1936 Contemportary Viewpoint
through Nov. 30, 1936 19th and 20th Century American Figure Paintings
circa 1936 Landscapes--Contemporary Viewpoint
Jan. 11-30, 1937 Selected Landscapes
Feb., 1937 Contemporary American Sculpture
March 15-April 3, 1937 Watercolors by Millard Sheets
April 12-30, 1937 John Whorf
April 27-May 16, 1937 Maurice Sterne
May, 1937 Paintings by American Artists
Summer, 1937 Paintings
Oct. 1-15, 1937 Recent Watercolors
Oct. 18-Nov. 6, 1937 Paintings by Lucille Blanche
Nov. 8-30, 1937 Paintings by American Artists
Dec. 6-24, 1937 Watercolors by Lester Field
Jan. 3-22, 1938 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Jan. 24-Feb. 5, 1938 Paintings by Margaret Cooper
Feb. 7-26, 1938 Colonial Portraits
March 7-26, 1938 Recent Oils and Watercolors by Millard Sheet
April 4-23, 1938 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
Summer, 1938 Paintings by American Artists
through Oct., 1938 Paintings by American Artists
Oct. 24-Nov. 12, 1938 Recent Watercolors by Karl Oberteuffer
Nov. 21-Dec. 17, 1938 Paintings for the Home by American Artists
Jan. 16-Feb. 4, 1939 Recent Paintings by Floyd Clymer
Feb. 6-25, 1939 Harry Hering
March 6-31, 1939 Figure Paintings by American Artists
April 3-22, 1939 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
May 15-June 3, 1939 Recent Watercolors by Millard Sheets
Summer, 1939 Selected Group of Paintings by American Artists
Sept., 1939 Paintings and Watercolors by American Artists
through Oct. 13, 1939 Recent Paintings by a Group of American Artists
Oct. 16-Nov. 4, 1939 Recent Paintings by Saul Schary
Nov. 13-Dec. 2, 1939 Toreros and Dancers of Spain and Mexico by Carlos Ruano Llopis
Dec., 1939 Paintings for the Home
Nov. 5-17 [193?] Table Portraits by Eulabee Dix
[193?] Paintings by American Artists
Jan. 2-27, 1940 Stephen Etnier
Feb. 12-March 2, 1940 Recent Watercolors by Robert Carson
March 11-30, 1940 Daniel Serra Paintings
April 8-27, 1940 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 28-May 18, 1940 Rubin Recent Paintings
through June 29, 1940 Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
through Sept. 28, 1940 Summer Exhibition of Paintings by a Selected Group of Early and Contemporary American Artists
Oct. 1-19, 1940 Recent Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Oct. 21-Nov. 9, 1940 Recent Watercolors by Allen Ingles Palmer
Nov. 18-Dec. 7, 1940 Helen Sawyer
Dec., 1940 Selected Paintings for the Home, and A Group of Original Studies in Color by Maurice Sterne
Jan. 13-Feb. 8, 1941 Watercolors by American Artists
Feb. 17-March 15, 1941 Paintings by Stephen Etnier, Sidney Laufman, and Francis Speight
April 7-26, 1941 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 28-May 17, 1941 Remembrances of South America and British West Indies by Manicol
May 19-June 30, 1941 Group of Paintings by Selected Contemporary American Artists
Summer, 1941 Exhibition of Selected Paintings by American Artists
Sept., 1941 A Selected Group of Paintings by Americna Artists
Oct. 6-25, 1941 Recent Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Oct. 27-Nov. 15, 1941 Eliot O'Hara Watercolors
Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1941 Recent Paintings by Jay Connaway
Nov. 17-Dec. 6, 1941 Recent Watercolors by Richard A. Kimball
Dec. 8-27, 1941 Edith Blum Paintings
Jan. 5-24, 1942 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
through Feb. 28, 1942 Selected Paintings by a Group of Contemporary American Artists
March 9-28, 1942 New Talents Presented by the Gloucester Society of Artists
April 6-25, 1942 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
May, 1942 Selected Paintings by Contemporary American Artists
June 2-13, 1942 Yun Gee
Summer, 1942 Selected Paintings by Early and Contemporary American Artists
Summer, 1942 Paintings by Selected American Artists
Oct. 5-31, 1942 Recent Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Nov. 9-30, 1942 Watercolors by American Artists
Jan. 18-Feb. 6, 1943 Paintings by Yovan Radenkovitch
April 4-24, 1943 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 26-May 15, 1943 Paintings and Watercolors by Childe Hassam
May 25-June 5, 1943 Exhibition by Gladys Irene Cook
June, 1943 Selected Paintings by American Artists
Summer, 1943 Exhibition of Paintings by American Artists
Sept., 1943 Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Oct. 4-23, 1943 Paintings by Yun Gee
Nov., 1943 Recent Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Jan. 24-Feb. 12, 1944 Recent Watercolors by James Fitzgerald
Feb. 14-March 4, 1944 Paintings by Sidney Laufman
March 6-25, 1944 Paintings by Jessie Ansbacher
April 3-22, 1944 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
May, 1944 Paintings by Important American Artists
Summer, 1944 Exhibition of Paintings by a Selected Group of American Artists
Summer, 1944 Exhibition of Selected Paintings by a Group of American Artists
Oct. 2-21, 1944 Recent Paintings by Jay Connaway
Oct. 23-Nov. 11, 1944 Harry Hering
Nov. 13-Dec. 2, 1944 Paintings by Hobson Pittman
Dec., 1944 Paintings for the Home by American Artists
Jan. 3-13, 1945 Paintings by Therese Steinhardt
Jan. 22-Feb. 10, 1945 Louis Ritman
Feb. 18-, 1945 Memorial Exhibition, Paintings and Pastels by William Henry Singer, Jr., N.A.
Feb. 19-March 10, 1945 Recent Watercolors by Eliot O'Hara, A.N.A. (Elect)
March, 1945 Paintings by a Selected Group of Contemporary Artists
April 9-28, 1945 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
May, 1945 Paintings by American Artists, Late 19th and Early 20th Century
Summer, 1945 Paintings by a Selected Group of Contemporary American Artists
Oct., 1945 Paintings by a Group of Selected American Artists
Oct. 22-Nov. 10, 1945 Helen Sawyer
Nov. 19-Dec. 1, 1945 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Nov. 19-Dec. 8, 1945 Hilde Kayn
Dec., 1945 Paintings for the Home by American Artists
Dec. 31-Jan. 19, 1946 Paintings by Stpehen Etnier
Jan. 28-Feb. 16, 1946 Paintings by Alexandra Pregel
Feb. 18-March 9, 1946 W.H. Singer
March 11-30, 1946 Paintings by American Artists
April 8-27, 1946 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
Summer, 1946 Paintings by 19th and 20th Century Americans
Oct. 7-26, 1946 Recent Watercolors by Allen Ingles Palmer
Oct. 28-Nov. 16, 1946 Paintings by Ferdinand Warren
Nov. 18-Dec. 7, 1946 Louis Di Valentin
Dec. 9-29, 1946 Recent Watercolors by Wm. F.C. Ewing and Richard A. Kimball
Jan., 1947 Paintings by Selected American Artists
Jan. 13-Feb. 1, 1947 Gerrit V. Sinclair Paintings
Feb. 3-21, 1947 Recent Watercolors by Jerri Ricci
Feb. 24-March 15, 1947 Childe Hassam Paintings
March 31-April 19, 1947 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 21-May 10, 1947 Pastels of Charleston by Hobson Pittman
June 2-13, 1947 Yun Gee
Oct. 6-25, 1947 Special Exhibition of American Paintings Honoring the Great Artists Who Have Been Shown in Our Galleries
Oct. 27-Nov. 15, 1947 New Paintings, Oil Studies, and Drawings by Leon Kroll
Nov. 17-Dec. 6, 1947 F. Douglas Greenbowe Watercolors
Jan. 19-Feb. 7, 1948 Paintings by Alexandria Pregel
March 22-April 3, 1948 American Art
March 22-April 3, 1948 Paintings by Artists Equity Association Members
May, 1948 Paintings by a Group of Selected American Artists
May 24-June 5, 1948 Paintings by New York Artists, 16th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 5-23, 1948 Impressions of New York
Oct. 25-Nov. 13, 1948 Paintings by Ernest Lawson
Nov. 15-27, 1948 Sculpture by Eleanor M. Mellon
Dec. 20-Jan. 8, 1949 Drawings by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 10-29, 1949 Six Watercolorists [Greenbowie, Knauth, Newman, Palmer, Ricci and Whorf]
Jan. 31-Feb. 19, 1949 New Paintings by Ferdinand Warren
Feb. 21-March 12, 1949 Paintings by Louis Di Vanentin
April 4-23, 1949 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 25-May 7, 1949 Paintings by Mildred Hayward
May 9-21, 1949 Paintings by New York Artists, 17th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
June 17-July 5, 1949 Paintings by Guy Pene DuBois
Oct. 4-29, 1949 Opening Exhibition of Paintings and Watercolors by 19th and 20th Century American Artists
Oct. 24-Nov. 12, 1949 Recent Watercolors by Henry Edmiston
Nov. 14-Dec. 3, 1949 Paintings by John H. Twachtman
Dec. 5-24, 1949 F. Douglas Greenbowe Watercolors
[194?] Paintings for the Home by American Artists
June [194?] 2-13Yun Gee
Jan. 9-28, 1950 Paintings by Gordon Samstag
Jan. 30-Feb. 18, 1950 George C. Ault Memorial Exhibition
Feb. 20-March 11, 1950 Recent Paintings by David Burr Moreing
March 13-April 1, 1950 Paintings by Frank di Gioia
April 3-22, 1950 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 24-May 13, 1950 Paintings by Contemporary American Artists
May 15-27, 1950 Paintings by New York Artists, 18th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 2-21, 1950 Recent Paintings by Benjamin Kopman
Nov. 13-Dec. 2, 1950 Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Dec. 4-30, 1950 Special Exhibition of American Paintings in Honor of the Philadelphia Museum of Art Diamond Jubilee
through Dec. 23, 1950 Watercolors and Drawings by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 8-27, 1951 New Gouaches of the Circus and Theatre by Walter Philipp
Jan. 29-Feb. 17, 1951 Louis Ritman Paintings
Feb. 19-March 10, 1951 Recent Watercolors by Jerri Ricci
March 12-31, 1951 Paintings, Panels, Figures of Africa, Belgian Congo, Bechuanaland, and Rhodesia by Jay Robinson
April 2-21, 1951 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 24-May 12, 1951 Sculpture and Drawings of Nicolaus Koni
May 21-June 1, 1951 Paintings by New York Artists, 19th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 22-Nov. 10, 1951 Recent Paintings by Thomas Blagden
Nov. 12-Dec. 1, 1951 Recent Paintings by David Burr Moreing
Dec., 1951 Group Exhibition
Jan. 7-26, 1952 Paintings of Italy and "Little Italy" by Frank di Gioia
Jan. 28-Feb. 16, 1952 London to Algiers, Recent Watercolors by Eliot O'Hara, N.A.
Feb. 18-March 8, 1952 Recent Paintings by Jacques Zucker
April 7-26, 1952 Recent Watercolors by John Whorf
April 28-May. 10, 1952 Paintings by Alexandra Pregel
May 12-24, 1952 Paintings by New York Artists, 20th Exhibition of the Arthur Schwieder Group
Oct. 28-Nov. 15, 1952 Paintings by John Sharp
Nov. 17-Dec. 6, 1952 Stephen Etnier: Recent Paintings
Dec. 8-27, 1952 Childe Hassam Watercolors
Jan. 5-24, 1953 Jay Robinson
Jan. 26-Feb. 14, 1953 Iver Rose